Friends, in this video you will learn how you
can renew the insurance policy of Google 2 or bike or any two wheeler in just 2 minutes. Watch this video carefully and completely
so that you can get complete information. So
you have to do one thing, first of all if
you have
an icon of Google 2 you have to
click on it and here you will search
bike insurance guys, you should not get confused, it is possible that
you have a scooter or a scooty, even then
you have to search for bike insurance here only,
okay, so you will
see here that many companies are coming
but right now there are
two insurance companies here, one is Digit Insurance and the
other is Aqua Insurance, okay, so here
first I will show you by
clicking on Digit Insurance and here
you will see that it is clearly written here that if
you directly click on the open website, then
their website will
open, let us come back
and here I will show you the policy of Aqua General
Insurance, as soon as I
click on it, then here I will
show you live on the open website.  If I
click, what will it do?
I had also made the payment of ₹ 229 here.
Okay, and remember, the
reason for making this video here was that
I already wanted to buy
a good insurance at the best and lowest price on paytmbank.com. So,
I have already
made a video on this and let me tell you
that for the last 5 years, I have been continuously getting a policy from the same company. So,
if you
want to know how you can do a bike insurance
policy yourself, if you want to do it for less money
and save money, then
you will get the link for it
in the description of the video. Go there and
after clicking, you will get the link
of the video. Watch that video and you will easily be able to do a
good and excellent
insurance policy at less money while sitting at home. Or friends, you
must tell us in the comments
which bike or scooter you have. Do comment and also
like the video because it takes a lot of hard
work to make a video and if you are stingy in liking it, then
please like it
and if possible, share this with your friends.  Do
share the video